TESSA SHERIN-SNIDAL

Graphic Designer—

CONTACT ME













(613) 447-8377







tessa@sherinsnidaldesign.ca

Gord McMillan Creative Director McMillan 541 Sussex Drive Ottawa, ON K1N 6Z6

REFERENCES

Dear Gord McMillan.

I am emailing you today to inquire into a possible placement at your company. I believe that I am the perfect fit for an internship at McMillan and, as such, I am enthusiastically applying to become part of your company.

As is stated in my attached resume, I have been in the Graphic Design program at Algonquin College now for 3 years and before that, received a major in Visual Arts from the University of Ottawa with a minor in Classical Studies; I have a varied background in design. Because of this varied background I would be a serious asset to you and the McMillan Agency and am an ideal candidate.

I work well to solve problems in both a team, and individually and as my attached resume explains I am very well suited for an internship in its many facets. I am a diligent and professional worker and represent those I am working for in this manner.

I hope that, after you review my attached resume, you will understand that I am the perfect fit for McMillian and I would love to set up a future interview to discuss my application for this internship.

Thank you very much for your time and consideration and I look forward to hearing from you.

Sincerely yours,

Tessa Sherin-Snidal

TESSA SHERIN-SNIDAL

Graphic Designer—

CONTACT ME



@sherinsnidaldesign



linkedin.com/in/tsherinsnidal



(613) 447-8377



sherinsnidaldesign.ca



tessa@sherinsnidaldesign.ca

OBJECTIVE

To find a company that provides me with an environment that encourages personal and professional development. To continuously grow and expand my skills as a designer, while being intellectually stimulated. To add value to the company by applying my knowledge and skills in creative strategy and design thinking.

EXPERIENCE

Waitress | Jack Astor's - Hunt Club | August 2015 - December 2017

Opening · Closing · Customer Service · Organization · Bartending

Waitress | Carleton Golf and Yacht Club | August 2012 - 2015

Opening · Closing · Customer Service · Organization · Bartending Event Planning · Event Setup · Member Account Charging & Maintenance

Sales Associate | Boathouse - Bayshore | July 2012 - February 2014

Opening · Closing · Cash Maintenance · Customer Service · Stock Maintenance Display Creator · Show Floor Maintenance · Cash Depositing · Staff Maintenance

Sales Associate | Truffle Treasures | September 2011-April 2012

Opening · Closing · Cash Maintenance · Customer Service · Stock Maintenance Display Creator · Show Floor Maintenance · Cash Depositing · Barista/Waitress

EDUCATION

Advanced Diploma in Graphic Design

April 2018 · Algonquin College

Bachelor of Arts - Honours in Visual Arts, Major in Classical Studies

April 2013 · University of Ottawa

Ontario Secondary School Diploma

June 2008 · South Carleton High School

<u>5</u>

APPLICATIONS





















UX/UI

Branding

Illustration







Motion

Print

Screen



Coding



Analytic



Synergy